A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.39 (A2014) FA760
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2014.003: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 2001-2014; AC_2014_003; 31.44 Cubic Feet 24 standard record storage boxes, R4389-R4412
  - PRD, 2010-2013; AC_2014_003_22; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 PRD 203 - SAMASOURCE, INC. - JOB CREATION IN KENYA, RWANDA AND UGANDA, 2010-2012 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRD 205 - WORLD VISION, INC. - FIELD-BASED SHARED SERVICE CENTER IN NAIROBI; BUSINESS PROCESS OUTSOURCING CENTERS IN TANZANIA AND GHANA, 2010-2013 (Box R4407)
  - PRE, 2009-2013; AC_2014_003_23; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2010 PRE 301 - CARNEGIE ENDOWMENT FOR INTERNATIONAL PEACE - NEW VISION BELLAGIO CONFERENCES, 2009-2011 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRE 302 - RESEARCH FOUNDATION OF STATE UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - FOUR YEAR FINANCIAL PLAN FOR NY STATE, 2009-2010 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRE 303 - CENTER FOR THE ADVANCEMENT OF WOMEN - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2009-2011 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRE 304 - UNIVERSITY OF DELAWARE - STUDY GROUP ON BOARDS OF DIRECTORS, 2010-2013 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRE 305 - FLORIDA INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY - FOUR FREEDOMS - TEEN THOUGHTS ON DEMOCRACY ONLINE, MATERIALS, 2010-2012 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRE 307 - DUKE UNIVERSITY - CENTER FOR STRATEGIC PHILANTHROPY AND CIVIL SOCIETY, 2010-2011 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRE 308 - MARY ROBINSON FOUNDATION (IRELAND) - EDUCATION AND WOMEN'S LEADERSHIP FOR CLIMATE JUSTICE, 2010-2013 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRE 309 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - INTERNATIONAL STUDY OF RADICALIZATION AND POLITICAL VIOLENCE PEACE AND SECURITY SUMMIT, 2010-2011 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRE 310 - MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - PUBLICATION - URBAN INNOVATION: NEW ORLEANS FIVE YEARS AFTER KATRINA, 2010-2011 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRE 311 - TULANE UNIVERSITY - NEW ORLEANS AS THE MODEL CITY FOR THE 21ST CENTURY SYMPOSIUM, 2010-2012 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRE 312 - GREATER WASHINGTON EDUCATIONAL TELECOMMUNICATIONS ASSOCIATION - WOMEN 2.0 MEDIA PROJECT, 2010-2012 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRE 313 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - PUBLICATION - STANFORD SOCIAL INNOVATION REVIEW, 2010-2012 (Box R4407)
    - 2010 PRE 314 - GREATER WASHINGTON EDUCATIONAL TELECOMMUNICATIONS ASSOCIATION - THE DUST BOWL FILM, 2010-2013 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 PRE 317 - JAZZ AT LINCOLN CENTER - ORCHESTRA RESIDENCY IN CUBA, 2010-2011 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 PRE 318 - PUBLIC-PRIVATE VENTURES - YOUNG ADULT SECTORAL INITIATIVE, 2010-2011 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 PRE 319 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - PENN MUSEUM COMMUNITY ENGAGAMENT, 2010-2012 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 PRE 320 - NATIONAL WOMEN'S LAW CENTER - CEDAW EDUCATION PROJECT, 2009-2011 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 PRE 321 - WOMEN'S CAMPAIGN INTERNATIONAL - AFRICAN FIRST LADIES INITIATIVE, 2010-2011 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 PRE 322 - CHERIE BLAIR FOUNDATION FOR WOMEN (ENGLAND) - WOMEN ENTREPRENEURS AND MOBILE TECHNOLOGY, 2010-2013 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 PRE 323 - CENTER FOR NATIONAL POLICY - GLOBAL SUMMIT ON RESILIENCE, 2010-2011 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 PRE 323 - Nine Eleven - Remembrance Renewal Resilience 10th Anniversary Summit - Digital, 2010-2011; 2014:003:049-2014:003:052 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 PRE 323 - Nine Eleven - Remembrance Renewal Resilience Tenth Anniversary Summit - Published Material, 2010-2011; 2014:003:070 (Box R4408)
  - RES, 2009-2013; AC_2014_003_24; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 RES 302 - BROOKINGS INSTITUTION - AFRICAN GROWTH INITIATIVE - INAUGURAL ANNUAL GROWTH FORUM CONFERENCE, 2010-2013 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 RES 303 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - USES OF INDICATORS FOR COMPLEX PROBLEMS OF DEVELOPMENT, 2010-2011 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 RES 308 - SOUTH AFRICA NODE OF THE MILLENNIUM PROJECT - INTERNET-BASED INFORMATION REPOSITORY AND NETWORKING PLATFORM, 2009-2012 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 RES 310 - BOSTON UNIVERSITY - ANALYSIS OF SEARCHLIGHT NEWSLETTERS, 2010-2012 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 RES 310 - Connecting the Dots - Information Visualization and Text Analysis of the Searchlight Project Newsletters - Published Material, 2010-2012; 2014:003:048 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 RES 311 - UNIVERSITY OF SUSSEX (ENGLAND) - NEW MODELS FOR TECHNOLOGY ASSESSMENT, 2010-2012 (Box R4408)
    - 2010 RES 314 - UNIVERSITY OF MANCHESTER (ENGLAND) - TREND AND HORIZON SCANNING - FORESIGHT JOURNAL, 2010-2012 (Box R4408)
  - SCG, 2010-2013; AC_2014_003_25; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 SCG 304 - RESEARCH FOUNDATION OF STATE UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - STATE GOVERNMENT TRANSFORMATION CHALLENGE PROJECT (1 FOLDER and 1 SUPPL), 2010-2013 (Box R4408)
  - SEG, 2009-2013; AC_2014_003_26; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 SEG 302 - LEHIGH CARBON COMMUNITY COLLEGE - GREEN ENERGY TRAINING CENTER, 2010-2011 (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SEG 303 - GREEN FOR ALL - COMMUNITY OF PRACTICE AND CAPITAL ACCESS PROGRAMS, 2009-2011 (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SEG 305 - INSTITUTE FOR SUSTAINABLE COMMUNITIES - CLIMATE ACADEMY ON TRANSPORTATION, 2009-2013 (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SEG 305 - ISC Grant - 2009 SRC 161 Attachments - Digital, 2009-2013; 2014:003:069 (Box R4409)
- AC.2014.012: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 2006-2014; AC_2014_012; 27.99 Cubic Feet 21 standard record storage boxes, R4413-4433, 1 letter document box and 1 clamshell box
  - THS, 2008-2014; AC_2014_012_1; 6.97 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes, 1 letter document box and 1 clamshell box
    - 2010 THS 317 - MERCY CORPS - CENTER FOR HEALTH MARKET INNOVATIONS IN INDONESIA, 2010-2012 (Box R4413)
    - 2010 THS 318 - INSTITUTE OF HEALTH POLICY, MANAGEMENT AND RESEARCH (KENYA) - CHMI EAST AFRICA HUB, 2010-2012 (Box R4413)
    - 2010 THS 319 - ACCESS HEALTH INTERNATIONAL - CENTER FOR HEALTH MARKET INNOVATIONS ACTIVITIES IN BRAZIL AND BANGLADESH, 2010-2012 (Box R4413)
    - 2010 THS 320 - CENTRE FOR HEALTH AND SOCIAL SERVICES (GHANA) - HEALTH SYSTEMS TRANSFORMATION IN AFRICA, 2010-2013 (Box R4413)
    - 2010 THS 323 - PATHFINDER INTERNATIONAL - mHEALTH INFORMATION-EDUCATION-COMMUNICATION SYSTEM IN VIETNAM, 2010-2011 (Box R4413)
    - 2010 THS 324 - UNITED NATIONS FOUNDATION - mHEALTH ALLIANCE, 2009-2013 (Box R4413)
    - 2010 THS 325 - PALLI KARMA-SAHAYAK FOUNDATION (BANGLADESH) - MICRO-HEALTH INSURANCE, 2010-2012 (Box R4413)
    - 2010 THS 331 - FREEDOM FROM HUNGER - CENTER FOR HEALTH MARKET INNOVATIONS ACTIVITIES IN THE ANDES REGION, 2010-2013 (Box R4413)
    - 2010 THS 332 - PHILIPPINE INSTITUTE FOR DEVELOPMENT STUDIES - CENTER FOR HEALTH MARKET INNOVATIONS, 2010-2012 (Box R4413)
    - 2010 THS 333 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - INITIATIVE TO IMPROVE KNOWLEDGE TRANSLATION ON HEALTH SYSTEMS AND POLICY ISSUES, 2010-2012 (Box R4413)
    - 2010 THS 335 - PHARMACCESS (NETHERLANDS) - ACCELERATION OF HEALTH CARE ACCREDITATION AND SYSTEMS IMPROVEMENT IN GHANA, 2010-2013 (Box R4413)
    - 2010 THS 338 - UNIVERSITY OF GHANA - HEALTH INFORMATICS ACTIVITIES, 2010-2012 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 THS 339 - CENTER FOR CREATIVE INITIATIVES IN HEALTH AND POPULATION (VIETNAM) - HEALTH MARKET INNOVATIONS, 2009-2012 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 THS 340 - BLOODLINK FOUNDATION (KENYA) - mHEALTH BLOOD DONOR MONITORING SYSTEM, 2010-2012 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 THS 341 - BRAC (BANGLADESH) - mHEALTH FOR MATERNAL NEONATAL AND CHILD HEALTH, 2010-2012 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 THS 343 - BANGLADESH ENTERPRISE INSTITUTE - SCENARIO PLANNING ON DIGITAL HEALTH BANGLADESH, 2010-2012 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 THS 345 - PUBLIC HEALTH FOUNDATION OF INDIA - UNIVERSAL HEALTH CARE SECRETARIAT, 2010-2012 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 THS 345 - High Level Expert Group Report on Universal Health Coverage for India - Digital Material, 2010-2012; 2014:012:002 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 THS 348 - CROWN AGENTS (UNITED KINGDOM) - HANSHEP SECRETARIAT, 2010-2013 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 THS 350 - WORLD FEDERATION OF PUBLIC HEALTH ASSOCIATIONS - NEW COMPETENCIES FOR PUBLIC HEALTH PROFESSIONALS, 2008-2012 (Box R4414)
    - 2011 THS 301 - WILLIAM J. CLINTON FOUNDATION - eHEALTH INFORMATION SYSTEM IN RWANDA, 2009-2013 (Box R4429)
    - 2011 THS 302 - LONDON SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND TROPICAL MEDICINE, UNIVERSITY OF LONDON (ENGLAND) - RFP: GOOD HEALTH AT LOW COST 2010, 2009-2013 (Box R4429)
    - 2011 THS 304 - MEDICAL CREDIT FUND (NETHERLANDS) - MIDWIFE TRAINING IN CHINA, 2011-2013 (Box R4429)
    - 2011 THS 305 - AFRICAN HEALTH ECONOMICS AND POLICY ASSOCIATION (UNITED KINGDOM) - TOWARDS UNIVERSAL HEALTH COVERAGE, CONFERENCE, 2011-2012 (Box R4429)
    - 2011 THS 306 - CAYETANO HEREDIA UNIVERSITY (PERU) - SYMPOSIUM ON MHEALTH STRATEGY FOR LATIN AMERICA (Box R4429)
    - 2011 THS 308 - FUNDACAO OSWALDO CRUZ (BRAZIL) - WORLD CONFERENCE ON SOCIAL DETERMINANTS OF HEALTH, 2011-2012 (Box R4429)
    - 2011 THS 308 - 3 pins - Memorabilia, 2011-2012; 2014:012:070 (Box SF 1)
    - 2011 THS 308 - Pictures of WCSDH October 2011 - Still Image, 2011-2012; 2014:012:067 (Box SF 2)
    - 2011 THS 309 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - STRATEGIC EHEALTH SUPPORT TO BANGALDESH, VIETNAM, AND THE PHILIPPINES, 2011-2012 (Box R4429)
    - 2011 THS 310 - NATIONAL BUREAU OF ASIAN RESEARCH - UHC WORKSHOP AT THE 2011 PACIFIC HEALTH SUMMIT (Box R4429)
    - 2011 THS 313 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - ENGAGING WITH THE G-8, PROVIDING FOR HEALTH INITIATIVE, 2011-2013 (Box R4429)
    - 2011 THS 314 - Program for Apporopriate Technology in Health, 2009-2013 (Box R4430)
    - 2011 THS 317 - African Population and Health Research Center (Kenya) - Health Systems Strengthening in Rwanda, 2011-2012 (Box R4430)
    - 2011 THS 319 - Asian Community Health Action Network (India) - People's Health Movement and UHC, 2011-2012 (Box R4430)
    - 2011 THS 320 - Chulalongkorn University (Thailand) - Course On Strategies For Private Sector Engagement and Public Private Partnership in Health, 2011-2012 (Box R4430)
    - 2011 THS 321 - Institute for Healthcare Improvement - Joint Learning Network Quality Track, 2011-2013 (Box R4430)
    - 2011 THS 322 - Centre for Health and Social Services (Ghana) - First Pan-African Conference On UHC, 2011-2013 (Box R4430)
    - 2011 THS 330 - Results For Development Institute - Lancet Special Series on UHC, 2011-2012 (Box R4430)
    - 2011 THS 331 - Reed Elsevier (United Kingdom) - Health System Reform in Asian Conference, 2011-2012 (Box R4430)
    - 2011 THS 333 - Council on Foreign Relations - UN General Assembly UHC Event, 2011-2013 (Box R4430)
    - 2011 THS 335 - Institute for Collaborative Development - African Health Policy Systems Bellagio Conference, 2011-2012 (Box R4430)
    - 2011 THS 336 - Women in Informal Employment: Globalizing and Organizing (United Kingdom) - Policy Dialogue on UHC and Working Poor, 2011-2013 (Box R4430)
    - 2011 THS 340 - World Health Organization (Switzerland) - eHealth Theme Special Bulletin, 2011-2012 (Box R4430)
    - 2011 THS 343 - Thammasat University (Thailand) - Workshop on Regional Health Laws, 2011-2012 (Box R4431)
    - 2011 THS 353 - China Medical Board - Health Education and Research in SE Asia, 2011-2013 (Box R4431)
    - 2011 THS 355 - Research, Training and Management International (Bangladesh) - Private Medical Schools Assessment, 2011-2013 (Box R4431)
    - 2011 THS 357 - Public Health Institute - mHealth Fellowships, 2011-2013 (Box R4431)
    - 2011 THS 358 - Carego International - Kenyan Health Information Exchange, 2011-2012 (Box R4431)
    - 2011 THS 360 - Instedd - iLab and eHealth Solutions, 2011-2013 (Box R4431)
    - 2011 THS 362 - Monitor Company Group - Health Innovation for Africa Challenge Fund, 2011-2012 (Box R4431)
    - 2011 THS 364 - Open Health Tools - Repository and Community Mangement Systems, 2011-2013 (Box R4431)
    - 2011 THS 365 - International Centre for Diarrhoeal Disease Research Bangladesh Health Insurance Project, 2010-2014 (Box R4431)
    - 2011 THS 366 - National Health Security Office (Thailand) - UC Training Center (Box R4431)
    - 2011 THS 368 - China National Health Development Research Center - National Provider Payment System, 2011-2013 (Box R4431)
  - TRA, 2008-2013; AC_2014_012_2; 6.57 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - 2010 TRA 301 - CENTER FOR CLEAN AIR POLICY - PROGRAM ON SUSTAINABLE TRANSPORTATION IN THE U.S., 2008-2012 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 TRA 303 - SECOND NATURE, INC. - TRANSPORTATION FOR AMERICA ADVOCACY CAMPAIGN, 2009-2011 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 TRA 305 - EDUCATIONAL BROADCASTING CORPORATION - BROADCASTING ON AMERICA'S INFRASTRUCTURE, 2008-2011 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 TRA305 - Blueprint America - Livable Future: Local Solutions - Digital Material, 2008-2011; 2014:012:003 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 TRA305 - WNET.ORG Thirteen, Blueprint America: Road to the Future - Digital Material, 2008-2011; 2014:012:004 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 TRA305 - Blueprint America - Beyond the Motor City - Digital Material, 2008-2011; 2014:012:005 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 TRA305 - Blueprint America - Blueprint America Series from North Carolina Now - Digital Material, 2008-2011; 2014:012:006 (Box R4414)
    - The Grass is Always Greener - Understanding Sustainability - Digital Material, 2008-2011; 2014:012:007 (Box R4414)
    - 2010 TRA 306 - MOSAIC FILMS, INC. - DOCUMENTARY, BEYOND THE MOTOR CITY (Box R4414)
    - 2010 TRA 307 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - TRANSPORTATION POLICY WORKING GROUP, 2010-2011 (Box R4415)
    - 2010 TRA 312 - MONITOR COMPANY GROUP LP - SCENARIO EXCERCISE FOR GRANTEES ON FEDERAL AUTHORIZATION (Box R4415)
    - 2010 TRA 315 - BUILDING AMERICA'S FUTURE - TRANSPORTATION AND INFRASTRUCTURE CHALLENGES IN U.S. CITIES, 2008-2011 (Box R4415)
    - 2010 TRA 316 - CEOs FOR CITIES - CRITIQUE OF THE URBAN MOBILITY REPORT, 2010-2011 (Box R4415)
    - 2010 TRA 320 - NATIONAL HOUSING CONFERENCE - CONFERENCE, PARTNERS IN INNOVATION, 2010-2011 (Box R4415)
    - 2010 TRA 322 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - SERIES OF PUBLICATIONS, 2010-2012 (Box R4415)
    - 2010 TRA 323 - REGIONAL PLAN ASSOCIATION - EMPIRE STATE FUTURE PROJECT, 2008-2012 (Box R4415)
    - 2010 TRA 324 - RECONNECTING AMERICA - TRANSIT CORRIDORS ACROSS THE U.S., 2010-2011 (Box R4415)
    - 2010 TRA 326 - ECONOMIC POLICY INSTITUTE - ECONOMIC SECURITY ISSUES AND WORKING FAMILIES, 2008-2012 (Box R4415)
    - 2010 TRA 329 - NATURAL RESOURCES DEFENSE COUNCIL - T4 BUSINESS CAMPAIGN, ENERGY SECURITY, 2009-2012 (Box R4415)
    - 2010 TRA 330 - INSTITUTE FOR THE ANALYSIS OF GLOBAL SECURITY - ADVOCACY COALITION ON ENERGY INDEPENDENCE, 2009-2012 (Box R4415)
    - 2010 TRA 333 - URBAN LAND INSTITUTE - WORKING GROUP ON LAND USE AND TRANSPORTATION, 2008-2013 (Box R4415)
    - 2010 TRA 335 - REGIONAL PLAN ASSOCIATION - AMERICA 2050 PROJECT, 2008-2012 (Box R4415)
    - 2011 TRA 301 - Policylink - National Transformation Policy Reform, 2008-2012 (Box R4431)
    - 2011 TRA 302 - Securing America's Future Energy Foundation - Transportation Policy and Energy Security, 2009-2012 (Box R4431)
    - 2011 TRA 202 - Northeast - Midwest Institute - Older U.S. Citites and Transportation, Infrastructure Issues, 2008-2013 (Box R4431)
    - 2011 TRA 305 - Tides Center - Apollo Alliance Project, 2009-2012 (Box R4432)
    - 2011 TRA 306 - Transportation Choices Coalition Transportation for Washington Campaign, 2009-2012 (Box R4432)
    - 2011 TRA 309 - Tri-State Transportation Campaign Federal Transportation Policy Advocate, 2009-2012 (Box R4432)
    - 2011 TRA 310 - Georgetown University - Regional Greenhouse Gas Inititative Meeting, 2010-2013 (Box R4432)
    - 2011 TRA 311 - Good Jobs First - Expanding Labor and Transit Rider Alliance, 2011-2012 (Box R4432)
    - 2011 TRA 314 - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace - Research Report, 2010-2011 (Box R4432)
    - 2011 TRA 317 - New America Foundation - Journalistic Exploration of Infrastructure Crisis, 2011-2013 (Box R4432)
    - 2011 TRA 318 - American Ideas Institute - American Conservative Center for Public Transportation, 2010-2012 (Box R4432)
    - 2011 TRA 319 - Bipartisan Policy Center - National Transportation Policy Project, 2008-2012 (Box R4432)
    - 2011 TRA 320 - Brookings Institute - Metropolitan Infrastructure Initiative, 2008-2012 (Box R4432)
    - 2011 TRA 321 - Southern Environmental Law Center - Transportation Advocacy in the Southeast, 2009-2012 (Box R4433)
    - 2011 TRA 323 - TCC Group - Evaluation Of Promoting Equitable and Sustainable Transportation, 2011-2013 (Box R4433)
    - 2011 TRA 324 - Natural Resources Defence Council - Sustainable Transit Campaign, 2010-2013 (Box R4433)
    - 2011 TRA 327 - Sustainable Mobility Finance 0 Bus Rapid Transit Innovations, 2011-2012 (Box R4433)
    - 2011 TRA 328 - Sustainable Mobility Finance - Bus Rapid Transit Innovation, 2011-2013 (Box R4433)
    - 2011 TRA 329 - Reconnecting America, Inc. - Transportation for America Campaign, 2010-2012 (Box R4433)
    - 2011 TRA 331 - Florida State University Research Foundation - Conference on Market-Based Solutions To Improve Public Transportation, 2011-2013 (Box R4433)
    - 2011 TRA 335 - Transformca - Bus Rapid Transit Model in East Oakland, California, 2011-2012 (Box R4433)
    - 2011 TRA 337 - North Carolina Metropolitan Mayors Coalition - Piedmont Crescent Partnership for Economic Growth, 2011-2013 (Box R4433)
  - Agriculture (AGR), 2011-2013; AC_2014_012_3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage boxes
    - 2011 AGR 301 - ALLIANCE FOR A GREEN REVOLUTION IN AFRICA - SUPPORT TO IMPROVE PRODUCTIVITY AND INCOMES OF SMALL-SCALE FARMERS, 2011-2013 (Box R4416)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center (BEL), 2011-2012; AC_2014_012_4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 BEL 302 - WONG HOY CHEONG - BELLAGIO CREATIVE ARTIST FELLOW, 2011-2012 (Box R4416)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Fellowships - Open in 2032
    - 2011 BEL 303 - PABLO CARDOSO - BELLAGIO CREATIVE ARTIST FELLOW (Box R4416)
    - 2011 BEL 304 - SUE WILLIAMSON - BELLAGIO CREATIVE ARTIST FELLOW, 2011-2012 (Box R4416)
    - 2011 BEL 305 - DARA BIRNBAUM - BELLAGIO CREATIVE ARTIST FELLOW, 2011-2012 (Box R4416)
    - 2011 BEL 307 - RESOURCE ALLIANCE LTD. (ENGLAND) - BELLAGIO SERIES ON THE FUTURE OF DEVELOPMENT AND PHILANTHROPY, 2011-2012 (Box R4416)
    - 2011 BEL 308 - INSTITUTE OF DEVELOPMENT STUDIES (ENGLAND) - BELLAGIO SERIES ON THE FUTURE OF PHILANTHROPY AND DEVELOPMENT, 2011-2012 (Box R4416)
    - 2011 BEL 309 - ALLIANCE OF ARTISTS COMMUNITIES - BELLAGIO MEETING ON INNOVATION AND EVALUATION IN ARTS RESIDENCIES, 2011-2012 (Box R4416)
  - Campaign for American Workers (CAW), 2011-2013; AC_2014_012_5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 CAW 301 - RESTAURANT OPPORTUNITIES CENTERS UNITED - PROMOTING THE HIGH ROAD PROJECT, 2011-2012 (Box R4416)
    - 2011 CAW 302 - PARAPROFESSIONAL HEALTHCARE INSTITUTE - DIRECT CARE WORKERS, 2011-2012 (Box R4416)
    - 2011 CAW 303 - NATIONAL EMPLOYMENT LAW PROJECT - LABOR RESEARCH AND POLICY, 2011-2013 (Box R4416)
    - 2011 CAW 304 - URBAN INSTITUTE - UNEMPLOYMENT AND RECOVERY INITIATIVE, 2011-2012 (Box R4416)
    - 2011 CAW 305 - MUJERES UNIDAS Y ACTIVAS - POLICY AGENDA AROUND AGING DOMESTIC WORKERS, 2011-2012 (Box R4416)
  - Climate Change Protection (CCP), 2008-2013; AC_2014_012_6; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 CCP 301 - ETHEKWINI MUNICIPALITY (SOUTH AFRICA) - CLIMATE CHANGE PROTECTION PROGRAMME, 2008-2012 (Box R4416)
    - 2011 CCP 301 - RF Report June 2012 Project Videos - Digital Material, 2008-2012; 2014:012:050 (Box R4416)
    - 2011 CCP 301 - Report to RF June 2012 Supporting Documentation - Digital Material, 2008-2012; 2014:012:051 (Box R4416)
    - 2011 CCP 302 - MARY ROBINSON FOUNDATION (IRELAND) - POLICY ADVOCACY ON CLIMATE CHANGE, 2011-2013 (Box R4416)
  - CEN, 2011-2013; AC_2014_012_7; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2011 CEN 301 - TENEO STRATEGY CONSULTING - CENTENNIAL PROGRAMMING (2 Files and 6 SUPPL EVENTS), 2011-2013 (Box R4417)
    - 2011 CEN 301 -Events 2011 Innovation Forum - Digital Material, 2011-2013; 2014:012:052-2014:012:055 (Box R4417)
    - Resilience Event Videos 2012 - Digital Material, 2011-2013; 2014:012:056, 2014:012:057 (Box R4417)
    - 2011 CEN 302 - KIVA MICROFUNDS - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2011-2012 (Box R4418)
    - 2011 CEN 303 - HEARTFILE (PAKISTAN) - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2011-2012 (Box R4418)
    - 2011 CEN 304 - AKIBA MASHINANI TRUST (KENYA) - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2011-2012 (Box R4418)
  - CIF, 2011-2013; AC_2014_012_8; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 CIF 302 - BROOKLYN ACADEMY OF MUSIC - RICHARD B. FISHER BUILDING, 2011-2013 (Box R4418)
    - 2011 CIF 315 - NEW YORK LIVE ARTS - NEW DANCE MODEL, 2011-2013 (Box R4418)
    - 2011 CIF 317 - CHIMPANZEE PRODUCTIONS - DIGITAL DIASPORA FAMILY REUNION, 2011-2013 (Box R4418)
  - Climate Change (CLI), 2008-2013; AC_2014_012_9; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 CLI 301 - INTEGRATED RESEARCH AND ACTION FOR DEVELOPMENT (INDIA) - POLICY ENGAGEMENT ON URBAN RESILIENCE, 2011-2012 (Box R4418)
    - 2011 CLI 302 - MERCY CORPS - COURSE ON URBAN CLIMATE CHANGE ADAPTATION IN BANGLADESH (Box R4418)
    - 2011 CLI 306 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL FOR LOCAL ENVIRONMENTAL INITIATIVES - AUSTRALIA-NEW ZEALAND - BUILDING RESILIENT CITIES IN INDONESIA, 2008-2011 (Box R4418)
    - 2011 CLI 308 - THE ENERGY AND RESOURCES INSTITUTE (INDIA) - NATIONAL POLICY ON URBAN RESILIENCE, 2011-2013 (Box R4418)
    - 2011 CLI 309 - INTELLECAP INC. - PRIVATE SECTOR AND CLIMATE CHANGE ADAPTATION IN INDIA, 2009-2011 (Box R4418)
  - CPR, 2010-2013; AC_2014_012_11; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2011 CPR 201 - ECOAGRICULTURE INTERNATIONAL - CLIMATE FINANCE LANDSCAPES IN AFRICA, 2011-2012 (Box R4418)
    - 2011 CPR 202 - PRICEWATERHOUSECOOPERS LIMITED (KENYA) - CARBON CREDITS IN AGRICULTURAL SYSTEMS, 2010-2012 (Box R4418)
    - 2011 CPR 205 - MERIDIAN INSTITUTE - CLIMATE CHANGE AND AGRICULTURAL PROJECT, 2011-2013 (Box R4419)
    - 2011 CPR 207 - FOOD AGRICULTURE AND NATURAL RESOURCES POLICY ANALYSIS NETWORK (SOUTH AFRICA) - ADVOCACY CAPACITY FOR CLIMATE SMART AGRICULTURE, 2011-2013 (Box R4419)
    - 2011 CPR 211 - NATURE CONSERVATION RESEARCH CENTRE (GHANA) - BUILDING CARBON BRIDGES ACROSS AMERICA, 2011-2013 (Box R4419)
  - CRD, 2011-2012; AC_2014_012_12; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 CRD 302 - ITAD LTD. (UNITED KINGDOM) - AFRICAN AGRICULTURE MONITORING AND EVALUATION, 2011-2012 (Box R4419)
    - 2011 CRD 305 - NETHOPE - WEATHER INFORMATION FOR DEVELOPMENT IN KENYA, 2011-2012 (Box R4419)
  - DOS, 2006-2011; AC_2014_012_13; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 DOS 301 - (ASSETS CAPACITIES) - DAY OF SERVICE DONATIONS, 2006-2011 (Box R4419)
  - DSN, 2007-2013; AC_2014_012_14; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 DSN 301 - ROYAL INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL AFFAIRS (ENGLAND) - GLOBAL HEALTH DIPLOMACY NETWORK ANNUAL MEETING, 2011-2012 (Box R4419)
    - 2011 DSN 302 - MINISTRY OF HEALTH, LAO P.D.R - MBDSN LEGAL ADVICE FOR INSTITUTIONALIZATION, 2011-2012 (Box R4419)
    - 2011 DSN 303 - REAL USEFUL TRAVEL AND MARKETING (KENYA) - DSN GRANTEES CONVENING, 2011-2012 (Box R4419)
    - 2011 DSN 304 - INTERNATIONAL LIVESTOCK RESEARCH INSTITUTE (KENYA) - ONE MEDICINE APPROACHES TO PARTICIPATORY EPIDEMOLOGY, 2008-2013 (Box R4419)
    - 2011 DSN 306 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - HEALTH EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT PROJECT IN EASTERN AFRICA, 2008-2013 (Box R4419)
    - 2011 DSN 308 - THAILAND - MINISTRY OF PUBLIC HEALTH - MBDS COOPERATION, 2007-2012 (Box R4419)
    - 2011 DSN 308 - Disaster Manual Edition 2 - Digital Material, 2007-2012; 2014:012:063 (Box R4419)
    - 2011 DSN 311 - UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA -GLOBAL HEALTH MOVEMENT, 2010-2013 (Box R4419)
  - EIN, 2010-2013; AC_2014_012_15; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage boxes
    - 2011 EIN 301 - NEW YORK ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - LANDSCAPING ON PLATFORM PROLIFERATION, 2011-2013 (Box R4420)
    - 2011 EIN 301 - NEW YORK ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - LANDSCAPING ON PLATFORM PROLIFERATION - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 2011-2013 (Box R4480A)